quatr.us 2016-03-28

# Quatr.us privacy policy - Quatr.us

## What information do we collect?

We don't collect any personal information from you when you visit our site.

## Information About Our Advertising Partners & The Information They Collect.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to this sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy [here](http://google.com/privacy_ads.html).  

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include  
Google Adsense   
Amazon   
Advertising.com  
Burst   
Valueclick   
Tribal Fusion   
Casale

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to choose the advertisements and links that appear on historyforkids.org. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. We also use Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting to get a general sense of who is visiting Quatr.us (whether they like sports, or music) so we can write pages you'll like more. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org or [Google Ad Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads).

Quatr.us has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Quatr.us's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

If you wish to disable cookies entirely, you can do that in your browser's Preferences settings.

## What do we use your information for?

To personalize your experience  
To improve our website  
To improve customer service

## How do we protect your information? 

Our advertisers implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information.

We don't use cookies, but our advertisers do. If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Quatr.us should work fine with cookies turned off.

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

Only to our advertisers, who do not use that information for any purpose other than choosing what ads to show you. They don't sell the information to anybody else. We are in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy or you wish to unsubscribe from our site and services you may contact us [by email](mailto:%20karen@historyforkids.org) or by writing to us at:

Kidipede/Karen Carr  
Department of History  
Portland State University  
Portland, OR 97207-0751  
United States

Also check out our cooking site at [Gevirts.com](http://www.gevirts.com/), and our children's site, [Kidipede](http://www.historyforkids.org/).

**Karen Eva Carr, PhD.**  
Assoc. Professor Emerita, History  
Portland State University

Read more

Professor Carr holds a B.A. with high honors from Cornell University in classics and archaeology, and her M.A. and PhD. from the University of Michigan in Classical Art and Archaeology. She has excavated in Scotland, Cyprus, Greece, Israel, and Tunisia, and she has been teaching history to university students for a very long time.

Less

**Help support Quatr.us!**

Quatr.us (formerly "History for Kids") is entirely supported by your generous donations and by our sponsors. Most donors give about $10. Can you give $10 today to keep this site running? Or give $50 to sponsor a page?
